[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"category": "Quick Math",
		"question": "Fred buys a hot chocholate. It's 20Â°C outside. How many avocados can a kangaroo eat within 10 minutes?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "15$"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Yes!"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "Bacon ipsum dolor amet filet mignon flank prosciutto"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"category": "Schwarzenegger",
		"question": "What did Arnold say?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Hello"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "I'll be black"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "get to the choppa"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"category": "Twitch Chat",
		"question": "Who is the coolest stream chat user?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Parralaxdicky"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Sylens__"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "kraft_durch_bier"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"category": "Chatter",
		"question": "Who is the coolest chatter?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Games_Maik"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Dummbatz"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "XRC_"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"category": "Beer",
		"question": "How much does it cost?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "15$"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "200$"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "26.5$"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"category": "Cucumbers",
		"question": "What did Arnold say?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Hello"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "I'll be black"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "get to the choppa"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"category": "?",
		"question": "Who is the coolest stream chat user?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Parralaxdicky"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Sylens__"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "kraft_durch_bier"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"category": "Spacing",
		"question": "Who is the coolest chatter?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Games_Maik"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Dummbatz"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "XRC_"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"category": "Bud Spencer",
		"question": "How much does it cost?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "15$"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "200$"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "26.5$"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"category": "Bud Light",
		"question": "What did Arnold say?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Hello"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "I'll be black"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "get to the choppa"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"category": "Butt Pics",
		"question": "Who is the coolest stream chat user?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Parralaxdicky"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Sylens__"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "kraft_durch_bier"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"category": "Nice",
		"question": "Who is the coolest chatter?",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": "a",
				"text": "Games_Maik"
			},
			{
				"id": "b",
				"text": "Dummbatz"
			},
			{
				"id": "c",
				"text": "XRC_"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": "a"
	}
]
